# **Deni Mintsaev**

### Front-end developer

#### **Contacts**

cube327@tuta.io denimintsaev.com github.com/dmint789 linkedin.com/in/deni-mintsaev

### **Skills**

HTML

CSS, SCSS, Less

Javascript, Typescript

Vue, Vuex, Nuxt

React, Redux

**React Native** 

**Express** 

MySQL

MongoDB

Docker

Nginx

Git, Github

Linux

# Languages

Russian - native

English - IELTS 8.0

Japanese - N2

German - A2

### **Education**

BA (Hons) Japanese Studies

#### **University of Manchester**

September 2018 - June 2022

Manchester, UK

# **Work Experience**

#### Web-Most | eljur.ru

#### Front-end developer (full-time)

October 2022 - present

• Rebuilding old pages using Vue and Less, adding new UI elements and features, and cleaning up legacy code for a website used for monitoring school attendance, grades, etc.

#### World Cube Association | worldcubeassociation.org

#### Full-stack developer (volunteer)

June 2021 - present

• Adding new features, porting old front-end code to React and fixing bugs using a tech stack with Ruby on Rails, React and MySQL, while working with a global team of developers.

# **Personal Projects**

### Kanji Sorter Web App

denimintsaev.com/kanjisorter

Sorts and filters Chinese or Japanese characters from the input in various ways. Aids in the process of learning the Chinese and Japanese writing systems.

### **Statistics Tracker Phone App**

github.com/dmint789/stat-tracker

Mobile app made in React Native used for tracking and sorting various daily statistics, like things related to hobbies, work, health, etc.

#### About Me

After over 10 years of programming, I have gained experience in many different IT fields, from system administration to mobile app development and even game development. My specialty is web development, where I have experience in creating full-stack websites and deploying them to Linux servers. It also helps that I use Linux myself and know a great deal about how to utilize the OS effectively. I also have experience with working in a team of developers, good leadership and communication skills, and the ability to learn new technologies at a rapid pace. I aim to work in a company with great potential, while continuing to improve my skills in web development and IT in general.